ERIC WARGIN

919-641-6335 iwmwargin@gmail.com LinkedIn

466 River Ridge Rd Boone, NC 28607

PERSONAL OBJECTIVE

With 20+ years of culinary experience, I'm excited to combine my past work experience with the new tools and skills I learned at the UNC Boot Camp. I'm eager to utilize my skillset to find a new career in the multi-faceted world of Full Stack Web Development.

EXPERIENCE

UNC Coding Full Stack Boot Camp — 2021 - 2022

6 month Boot Camp where I learned front end and back end of web development with a focus on Javascript.

With the skills I learned during the course I completed over 20 individual projects and 3 group projects. I enjoyed working with classmates with different skill sets to achieve fully functioning applications that used Javascript, API's, databases, etc.

With the help of a few classmates we developed three separate applications:

Date Night at Home — An app that upon entering what dish you'd like to make provides you with a recipe and ingredient list for said dish, as well as a wine pairing to how with it.

This app was created using Git, HTML, CSS, Bulma, Tasty API and Spoonacular API.

Friendless in Seattle — An app that allows you to connect with people online or offline depending on where you live and what your interests are.

This app was created using Git, HTML, CSS, Bulma, JavaScript, JQuery, Handlebars, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, and an API that randomly generates an Avatar based on the username.

Disco at the Dungeon — A React App digital stat tracker for your Dungeons and Dragons campaign.

This is a MERN stack single-page application that was created using GraphQL, MongoDB,Express.js, Node.js, JWT, Apollo, React, CSS, and Bulma.

Chef, The Little School at Duke; Durham, NC — 2017-2022

Created weekly menus for 150 kids plus 35+ staff members. This involved 30+ kids that had dietary restrictions that had to be followed closely to prevent allergic reaction or sickness.

Responsible for ordering of all food products and ingredients as well as maintaining all equipment, small wares, etc.

Created partnerships with local companies such as CompostNow and GreenToGo to eliminate waste and promote composting and recycling.

Chef/General Manager, The Farmery; RTP, NC - 3/16 - 11/17

Responsible for running most aspects of a new start-up; duties ranged from hiring and staff management, sourcing of local products, developing relationships within the community and ordering/management of all goods.

Responsible for menu costing and analysis. Communicated with owner to anticipate needs from the indoor state of the art growing systems kept on premise and elsewhere.

EDUCATION

UNC-Chapel Hill — Coding Full Stack Boot Camp — 2021-2022
Johnson and Wales University — A.S. Culinary Arts — 3.87 GPA 2005-2006

SKILLS

Experience in Javascript, HTML5, React, NodeJS, CSS, Git, among others

18+ years management experience, including conflict management and communication, team-building, project planning, analytical thinking, attention to detail, creativity, high adaptability and time management.

REFERENCES

Chris Jones - Chef at Little School at Duke - 919-360-0073

Chris Burgess - Chef at Little School at Duke and Hillsborough - 919-619-1898

Jasper Rajendren - Owner Sparrow Cafe Minneapolis - 612.207.6807

Lyndsey Clevesy - Classmate UNC Coding Boot Camp - 910-228-6617